+251939186449

# MARAMAWIT DEREJE

maramawitdereje93@gmail.com

Computer Engineer

Dire Dawa ,Ethiopia

## **SUMMARY**

I am product manager with holistic knowledge of website development and design. I also have experience training users from various organizations. As a product manager, I make sure that products fulfill customer needs and corporate goals throughout their whole lifecycle, from conceptualization to launch. In my capacity as a system administrator, I ensured seamless operations and strict security guidelines throughout the company by maintaining and optimizing the IT infrastructure concurrently. In addition, my proficiency as a website developer enables me to design aesthetically attractive and intuitive online platforms that improve brand visibility and encourage user interaction.

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science Degree in Electrical and Computer Engineering (Computer Engineering) 2018–2024

### SKILLS

- Basic user in Microsoft Office MS Word, MS Access, MS Excel and MS Power point.
- Computer software maintenance.
- Familiar with Programming languages HTML, CSS/ Bootstrap, WordPress JavaScript, PHP/CodeIgnitor, MySQL, C++ and React Js(Node Js).
- Product Management

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Product Manager**

Afronex tech hub | Oct 2023 - present

- Conduct day-to-day project coordination and
- implementation across different organization.
- Give training for various government organizations and non government .

### **System Adminstrator**

Afronex tech hub | Oct 22/2022 - Oct 19/2023

 make sure an organization's computer systems are functioning and meet the needs of the organization.

# Website Developer From 2022-2024

• Create functional, user-friendly websites and web applications using WordPress , HTML & CSS ,Code igniter and React Js